<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homepage on Jammy</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in Homepage on Jammy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://demo-shop.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Boy and His Blob</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a558a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a558a/</guid><description>SWITCH LIMITED RUN #149
When the planet of Blobolonia fell under the tyrannical rule of the evil Emperor, one brave blob managed to flee in search of help. After crash landing on Earth, the blob finds an unlikely hero in a young boy. Together they must return to Blobolonia and defeat the evil Emperor. Armed with nothing but the power of friendship and a bag full of jelly beans that can transform the blob into fun and versatile tools, this pair of heroes has all they need to take you on an unforgettable adventure.</description></item><item><title>A Little Golf Journey</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4yya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4yya/</guid><description>Limited Run Games UNLOCK SECRETS, DISCOVER TREASURE, AND TAKE ON CHALLENGES. YOUR GOLFING JOURNEY AWAITS.
JOIN US ON A LITTLE GOLF JOURNEY Embark on your adventure and bring color back to the world as you complete golfing challenges across multiple destinations. With over 100 holes split across 10 stunning courses, you’ll be able to unlock secrets and discover mysteries along the way.
Who knows what awaits you on your journey?</description></item><item><title>A Monster's Expedition + Earlier Adventures</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a643a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a643a/</guid><description>This collection is an absolute feast for puzzle fans. For nearly a decade, Draknek &amp;amp; Friends have been crafting bespoke, lovingly designed puzzle experiences that take a theme, mechanic, or ludicrous idea and push it to its natural conclusion. This collection features four of these award-winning experiences, packaged together on a single Nintendo Switch cartridge for over 100 hours of head-scratching goodness.
The crown jewel of this collection is A Monster’s Expedition, an open-world puzzle adventure that casts players as a monster exploring an archipelago museum of human culture.</description></item><item><title>Adventure Academia: The Fractured Continent</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a585b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a585b/</guid><description>The Continent of Pedra, home to four nations, is in the midst of a serious crisis. The entire island is slowly transforming into a labyrinthine dungeon, and monsters are roaming the lands&amp;hellip;
Cue our charming protagonist, Alex, who sets out on a journey in search of his missing father.
Using the Ruler Orb, a tactical artifact passed down in his family for generations, Alex has the ability to command others on the battlefield.</description></item><item><title>Annulled</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/annulled/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/annulled/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Are You Smarter than a 5th Grader?</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4cpa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4cpa/</guid><description>Are You Smarter Than A 5th Grader? for Nintendo® Switch is a charmingly humorous quiz game based on the popular TV franchise. Multiple-choice questions, true-or-false challenges, and minigames will test your proficiency in 24 different subjects. Faced with a tough question, you can always rely on your classmates for help. More than 6800 questions on topics like animal sciences, vocabulary, math, and more are delivered by a diverse, fully voiced, and animated cast of characters.</description></item><item><title>Astalon: Tears of the Earth</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2r8a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2r8a/</guid><description>LIMITED RUN #138 Relive the glory days of 8-bit action-adventure through beautifully detailed, authentic pixel art set in a dark, fantastic world! Astalon features the progressive exploration of an interconnected world with the swiftness and quick rhythm of a room-by-room action platformer.
Original character design by Ryusuke Mita, creator of world-famous manga Dragon Half! Play at your own pace &amp;ndash; explore thoroughly and build your characters strengths, or use risky methods to slice your way up the tower furiously!</description></item><item><title>Astro Aqua Kitty - Pawsome Collection</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5ada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5ada/</guid><description>ASTRO AQUA KITTY PAWSOME COLLECTION INCLUDES Astro Aqua Kitty Aqua Kitty UDX Stickers
ASTRO AQUA KITTY The Aqua Kitty cats have launched into space in an all new action RPG shoot-em-up adventure!
Pick your crew, then blast off to investigate mysterious water filled asteroids.
Battle bizarre enemies, mine magnificent gems, grab new weapons, install enhancing devices, and unlock your crews&amp;rsquo; unique skills as you level up XP.
Just watch out for marauding pirate rabbits, always trying to be first to the loot!</description></item><item><title>Axiom Verge &amp;amp; Axiom Verge 2</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6c2a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6c2a/</guid><description>You may have played Axiom Verge, or heard it referenced as a benchmark for indie action-exploration games. This long awaited sequel expands on the universe with completely new characters, abilities, and gameplay.
Indra, the billionaire behind the worldwide Globe 3 conglomerate, heads to Antarctica to investigate the disappearance of her daughter, but ultimately finds herself in entirely different reality, infected by parasitic machines that both aid and confound her. Where is she?</description></item><item><title>Aztech Forgotten Gods</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3pga/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3pga/</guid><description>Aztech Forgotten Gods is the cyber-stone action-adventure following Achtli, a young woman who battles the colossal Forgotten Gods. To uncover the truth behind her far-future Mesoamerican metropolis, she&amp;rsquo;ll have to turn the Gods&amp;rsquo; power against them, as she soars through the city with power and grace.</description></item><item><title>Azure Striker GUNVOLT 3</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a325a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a325a/</guid><description>The next installment in the high-speed 2D action Gunvolt series is finally here with Azure Striker Gunvolt 3. Balancing both an involving story and satisfying gameplay, Gunvolt 3 is the most extravagant entry in the series yet!
Play as both new star Kirin and series protagonist Gunvolt as you switch between them on the fly while conquering Gunvolt 3&amp;rsquo;s many stages and bosses. Story Mode+ which keeps the exciting action uninterrupted by the rich story.</description></item><item><title>Behind the Frame: The Finest Scenery</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6r4a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6r4a/</guid><description>A relaxing, eloquent experience that can be played at any pace. Become immersed in a panoramic world filled with resplendent colors, beautiful hand-animated visuals, and a smooth, easy-listening soundtrack.
As a passionate artist, seek the missing colors that will bring your paintings to life - all while remembering to take the occasional coffee and breakfast breaks that keep you going. There is more than what meets the eye, for every painting has a story to tell!</description></item><item><title>Blaster Master Zero 3</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3jxa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3jxa/</guid><description>LIMITED RUN #109
Blaster Master Zero 3&amp;rsquo;s hybrid of sidescrolling and top-down action is back for its 3rd chapter, and more intense than ever before! Series protagonist Jason travels to where the series all began, the planet Sophia, in order to save series heroine Eve in this final installment of the BMZ trilogy.
In the previous game, Blaster Master Zero 2, Jason and his partner Eve finally reach their destination, the planet Sophia, after a long and arduous journey through space.</description></item><item><title>Blaster Master Zero Trilogy: MetaFight Chronicle</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a337a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a337a/</guid><description>Blaster Master Zero One day, a young man named Jason Frudnick, known for being a genius in the field of robotic engineering, discovered a strange creature that he had never seen before. No records of this mysterious creature could be found, so Jason gave it the name &amp;quot; Fred &amp;quot; and took it to his lab to begin closely observing it.
Shortly after that, an accident occurred in the lab and Fred managed to escape.</description></item><item><title>BloodRayne Betrayal: Fresh Bites</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a25da/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a25da/</guid><description>The Brimstone Society has summoned Rayne for one last mission to lead a group of soldiers into a giant underground castle to do battle against none other than her own father, Kagan. When her escort proves ineffective against Kagan’s supernatural forces, it’s up to Rayne to run, jump, cut, and feed her way through gruesome foes, deadly traps, tricky platforming sections, and horrifying bosses. It’s Rayne’s last job — will she “clean house” or find herself six feet under?</description></item><item><title>Cart</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/cart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/cart/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Chaos</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6w2b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6w2b/</guid><description>Chaos;Head Noah
&amp;quot;If you were God, and your delusions could become reality. What kind of delusions would you imagine? A sensual world? A dystopic society? Destructive punishment? Or&amp;hellip;&amp;quot;
Nishijou Takumi, a shut-in gamer and anime otaku, spends his days locked away in a shipping container while occasionally attending classes. In his place of residence, Shibuya, a bizarre string of serial killings is set in motion as he is dragged into the ordeal.</description></item><item><title>checkout</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/before-stripe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/before-stripe/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Cozy Grove</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2fkj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2fkj/</guid><description>Come for the view, stay for the friends.
Welcome to Cozy Grove, a life-sim game about camping on a haunted, ever-changing island. As a Spirit Scout, you&amp;rsquo;ll wander the island&amp;rsquo;s forest each day, finding new hidden secrets and helping soothe the local ghosts. With a little time and a lot of crafting, you&amp;rsquo;ll bring color and joy back to Cozy Grove!
Cozy Grove is synced to real-world time and provides 30-60 minutes of new quest content each day.</description></item><item><title>Crisis Core - Final Fantasy VII - Reunion</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6j6a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6j6a/</guid><description>CRISIS CORE -FINAL FANTASY VII- REUNION, a remaster of PlayStation Portable exclusive, CRISIS CORE -FINAL FANTASY VII-. The 2007 cult classic action RPG and prequel to FINAL FANTASY VII. CRISIS CORE -FINAL FANTASY VII-REUNION is a true remaster that follows the original story of SOLDIER 1st Class Zack Fair on his mission to find missing SOLDIER Genesis Rhapsodos, unraveling the stories of Cloud, Sephiroth, Aeith, Tifa and more.</description></item><item><title>Curse of the Sea Rats</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2mxa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2mxa/</guid><description>Curse of the Sea Rats is a ‘ratoidvania’ platform adventure with lovingly crafted, hand-drawn animations. Embark on the epic journey of four prisoners of the British empire, transformed into rats by the notorious pirate witch, Flora Burn. To regain their human bodies, they will have to fight dangerous bosses, uncover the secrets of the vast Irish coast, and ultimately capture the witch who cursed them.</description></item><item><title>Dawn of the Monsters</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a446a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a446a/</guid><description>SWITCH LIMITED RUN #136
The cataclysmic battle between giant monsters has begun in this manga-inspired, side-scrolling, kaiju beat-&amp;rsquo;em-up! Titanic creatures known as Nephilim have invaded Earth, and the only hope of stopping them is DAWN (Defense Alliance Worldwide Network), which unleashes its own colossal combatants to defend against the enemy hordes! Take control of four hulking behemoths – Megadon, Aegis Prime, Tempest Galahad, and Ganira – each with distinct abilities and play styles, and smash your way through destructible real-world environments spanning more than 35 missions!</description></item><item><title>Demon Throttle</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a46qa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a46qa/</guid><description>Introducing Demon Throttle by developer Doinksoft, the creators of Gato Roboto. Coming to Nintendo Switch as a physical box - and only a physical box set. DEMON THROTTLE is a true collector&amp;rsquo;s edition&amp;hellip; of an amazing NEW game. This game premieres in 2022, when you get it in the mail. It will not be available digitally.
Demon Throttle tells the story of a beautiful vampiress and dusty gunslinger on a quest for vengeance against a demon that stole her mystical chalices and slept with his estranged wife.</description></item><item><title>Demon Turf</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4zwa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4zwa/</guid><description>SWITCH LIMITED RUN #143
The Demon World is inhabited by all kinds of nasties&amp;hellip; Most of them lumped into gangs battling for dominion, each led by its own head honcho. Yet even these bad dudes are no match for the Demon King himself! Instead, the task falls to Beebz, a young demon barely a thousand years old, who decides it’s time for her to kick every turf leader’s butt and become the Demon Queen herself.</description></item><item><title>Doom: The Classics Collection</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4kya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4kya/</guid><description>Limited Run # 102 Includes three classic DOOM games preserved on one cartridge - DOOM, DOOM II, and DOOM 3! No game downloads required. These classic games popularized the first-person shooter and allow players to wield an arsenal of powerful weapons as you battle demon hordes on Mars, on Earth, and across Hell. DOOM: You’re one of Earth’s toughest marines stationed on mars when a military experiment opens the gates to hell.</description></item><item><title>Dragon Star Varnir</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2r3b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2r3b/</guid><description>In a world where the bones of an ancient beast tower over the land&amp;hellip;​​
The Knight Zephy is part of an order whose role is to hunt down witches – people seen as cursed beings for giving birth to dragons.​​
He is brutally mauled by a dragon on one mission, but as he gasps his last breath, two witches save him by feeding him dragon blood – a death-defying magical substance that also grants him new witch powers.</description></item><item><title>DreamWorks Dragons: Legends of The Nine Realms</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4nxa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4nxa/</guid><description>Unleash your inner dragon and fly beyond the Hidden World, on your fiery adventure to rescue Thunder’s family and save the dragon kingdoms!
Feel the wind against your scales as you soar and dive through unexplored realms. Use your speed, tail, and claws to defeat the worthy foes and gigantic dragon bosses that stand in your way. Level up Thunder and his friends to become the ultimate dragon heroes by choosing new unlockable skills and powers.</description></item><item><title>Dusk Diver 2</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a59zb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a59zb/</guid><description>Enter Taiwan’s bustling district of Ximending, a destination for gourmands, music aficionados – and interdimensional beings intent on destroying this world!
One year after saving humanity from dimensional destruction, Yumo and the Guardians of Kunlun take on new forces in a sequel packed with even more hack n slash gameplay. Switch control of four unique characters, get stat boosts from real-life restaurant meals, and tailor skills and Orb combos to suit your play style!</description></item><item><title>Eiyuden Chronicle: Rising</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5rca/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5rca/</guid><description>Eiyuden Chronicle: Rising combines a thrilling adventure through ancient ruins with the tale of one town’s rise from the ashes.
Drawn by lenses and other treasures in the nearby Runebarrows, our heroes learn that the town is struggling to rebuild after an earthquake and decide to help. Along the way, they’ll resolve disputes between eager adventurers and wary locals who don’t think the Barrows should be disturbed. And they’ll learn more about each other’s reasons for seeking treasure, deepening their bonds in the process.</description></item><item><title>Error 404</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/404.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/404.html</guid><description/></item><item><title>Five Nights at Freddy's</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2a2a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2a2a/</guid><description>Welcome to your new job at Freddy Fazbear’s Pizza – where fantasy and fun come to life! Discover why children and adults alike love Freddy and his animatronic friends as you survive a series of terrifying encounters with the cast of murderous machines that roam the halls of the pizzeria at night looking for unwelcome visitors. Remember: Fazbear Entertainment is not responsible for accidental or intentional death or dismemberment.
Five Nights at Freddy&amp;rsquo;s [Core Collection] includes:</description></item><item><title>Golden Force</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2qka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2qka/</guid><description>The King of Demons sets his sights on Muscle Island, a peaceful paradise where life is good and all is well. Yet this evil monster sends in his army and attacks the populace with the help of his Wasting their last coins in the island’s taverns, mercenaries from the powerful Golden Force enjoy their last moments of vacation when they receive a new contract: defeat this evil threat in order to win back the Gold Mountain now in the Demon King’s possession.</description></item><item><title>Gunvolt Chronicles: Luminous Avenger iX 2</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5p3b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5p3b/</guid><description>Luminous Avenger iX 2 takes the series&amp;rsquo; original speedy and stylish 2D action gameplay to the next level as Copen rips through enemies with his new &amp;quot;Break-Shift&amp;quot; form. His new destructive capabilities makes the high-speed action more satisfying than ever! INTI CREATES is proud to present new apeX of cutting-edge 2D action with Luminous Avenger iX 2!
●2D action that breaks new ground!
With his new spinning blade weapon, the Razor Wheel, Copen rips through any enemy standing in his way as he traverses an enormous tower.</description></item><item><title>Hello Neighbor 2</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4t3a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4t3a/</guid><description>Hello Neighbor 2 is the sequel to the popular stealth horror game about sneaking into your creepy neighbor&amp;rsquo;s house. You play as a local journalist investigating missing person reports when you follow a series of clues leading you back to the abandoned house of The Neighbor.
The only problem is, that it&amp;rsquo;s occupied by a mysterious crow-like being. The only logical thing to do is break in. Welcome back to Raven Brooks.</description></item><item><title>Hokko Life</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a598a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a598a/</guid><description>Step off the train into the town of Hokko and get settled into your new home!
This quiet village needs your help to turn it into the charming rural town everyone loves. With hammer and paints in hand it&amp;rsquo;s up to you to design, build and decorate homes for all of your new friends!
Get Creative!
Busy yourself away in the dusty old workshop and let your creativity flow!
Craft materials and combine them in whatever way you desire to create new and wonderful furniture and items for your town.</description></item><item><title>Horgihugh And Friends</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4u6b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4u6b/</guid><description>Shoot down 16-bit bad guys in Horgihugh and Friends!
At the end of a brutal war, countries decided to dismantle their weapons. When the Gozareans attack, two retired pilots realize their trusty vintage fighter planes are the only means of combating the alien’s powerful weapon-nullifying technologies. Taking to the skies, Hugh and Figaro are the world’s last wings of hope.</description></item><item><title>Kirby's Return to Dream Land Deluxe</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2jya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2jya/</guid><description>The tough puff Kirby is back for a 4-player* platforming adventure. Copy enemies’ abilities and use their power to attack with a sword, wield a whip, and float with a parasol. You can also laser blast with the new Mecha Copy Ability that makes a series debut! The extra muscle will be handy in finding missing pieces for Magolor’s ship, which crash landed on Planet Popstar. Float and fight along with friends on the same system, where each player can control another Kirby or one of Kirby’s iconic friends like King Dedede, Meta Knight, and Bandana Waddle Dee.</description></item><item><title>L.O.L. Surprise! B.B.s Born To Travel</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6ssa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6ssa/</guid><description>Fans around the world can&amp;rsquo;t wait to unbox their own L.O.L. Surprise! doll - and you&amp;rsquo;re about to make their dreams come true! Choose your character and bring the L.O.L. Surprise! doll store to life, as you collect fierce dolls with glitter, hearts, diamonds, and more. No matter your age, there&amp;rsquo;s just enough challenge to bring out the fierce L.O.L. Surprise! doll-maker in you!
This trip around the world is full of surprises!</description></item><item><title>LEGO Brawls</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6aua/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6aua/</guid><description>Dream up the ultimate Minifigure brawlers and bash your way through all of your favorite LEGO® themes in the first team action brawler set in the LEGO universe. Play with friends at home or around the world and see how you stack up against the competition.
BUILD THE ULTIMATE BRAWLER Design your ultimate LEGO Minifigure hero with unique style, strategy and personality. A cactus with an attitude? A scrappy janitor ninja who happens to have fighting chickens?</description></item><item><title>Let's Play Curling!!</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a53yb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a53yb/</guid><description>Genuine Curling is now on the Nintendo Switch™!
Utilize simple controls to make that all-important game-winning throw!
It&amp;rsquo;s curling that anyone can pick up and play! Just aim for the target, adjust your strength, and shoot! Use your Joy-Con™ to sweep!
Familiarize yourself with the rules and controls with an easy-to-follow tutorial. Consult the glossary at any time for curling terms, rules, and tips.</description></item><item><title>Life in Willowdale: Farm Adventures</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6v3a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6v3a/</guid><description>Welcome to Willowdale, your life of farming and adventure starts here!
The once-thriving town of Willowdale is in ruins! The mayor’s business-minded daughter Penny has seized the opportunity to transport this once pleasant place into a high-flying modern tourist destination. She doesn’t really like animals and thinks keeping livestock is dirty especially when you can import all these products easily from a nearby town. With humans and nature so out of balance… some animals felt abandoned and had already left.</description></item><item><title>Little League World Series Baseball 2022</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5mga/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5mga/</guid><description>Become a Little League World Champ: Choose your team, then showcase your skills as you compete through the bracket to see if you have what it takes to be named the Little League World Series Champion. Or jump right into the action in an instant with Quick Play mode. Play With Friends: Get together for exciting local multiplayer tournament action for up to four players. Customize the rules, select your stadium and teams, and see who wins it all!</description></item><item><title>Loop Hero</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4taa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4taa/</guid><description>Infinite Adventure: Select from unlockable character classes and deck cards before setting out on each expedition along a randomly generated loop path. No expedition is ever the same as the ones before it Plan Your Struggle: Strategically place building, terrain, and enemy cards along each loop to create your own dangerous path. Find balance between the cards to increase your chances of survival while recovering valuable loot and resources for your camp Loot and Upgrade: Strike down menacing creatures, recover stronger loot to equip on the fly and unlock new perks along the way Expand Your Camp: Turn hard-earned resources into campsite upgrades and gain valuable reinforcements with each completed loop along the expedition path Save the Lost World: Overcome a series of unholy guardian bosses over a grand saga to save the world and break the time loop of the Lich</description></item><item><title>Love Esquire</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2yrb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2yrb/</guid><description>In Love Esquire, you&amp;rsquo;re not a famous knight, but a good-for-nothing squire who&amp;rsquo;s on a quest to find man&amp;rsquo;s greatest pleasure. Getting the girl won&amp;rsquo;t be easy though, since most of them are waaaay out of your league!
So raise those stats, battle monsters, and unleash your full potential!
FEATURES
♡ 5 Dateable Waifus – Love Esquire&amp;rsquo;s heroines are not just pretty faces! Each have their own unique ambitions, backstories, plots, and dirty little secrets for you to uncover.</description></item><item><title>Mail Mole - Collector's Edition</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3aye/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3aye/</guid><description>We are presenting our new hero, Molty, the mail mole! Moving underground, climbing massive walls and soaring through the skies, there’s no place our hero can’t reach! Traveling with Cannon Lines, Molty must overcome the most complicated challenges to reach Carrotland‘s furthest mailboxes: bottomless pits, quicksands, avalanches, floating platforms, sharp spikes&amp;hellip; a tough road. But when the power is out, you can’t send an email! Embark on an adventure that will force you to make the most important delivery of your life.</description></item><item><title>Mario + Rabbids: Sparks of Hope</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2g7a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2g7a/</guid><description>Team up with Mario, Luigi, Princess Peach, Rabbid Peach, Rabbid Luigi, and their friends on a galactic journey to defeat a malevolent entity and save your Spark companions. Explore planets throughout the galaxy as you uncover mysterious secrets and compelling quests!
•Build your dream team with three heroes from an eclectic roster of nine. •Take down all new bosses, along with some familiar enemies throughout the galaxy. •Rescue the adorable Sparks throughout the galaxy, who provide distinct powers that will help you in battle.</description></item><item><title>Mercenaries Rebirth: Call of the Wild Lynx</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4zcc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4zcc/</guid><description>Obtain the sword of victory together with Princess Kiera and the Wild Lynx Mercenaries! Mercenaries Rebirth is a tactical RPG set in a fantasy world.
Battles occur on quarter-view maps with height differences, wherein the front, back, and side of the map determine each battle’s outcome. Support effects depend on where allied characters from your party are in position, etc., features of high strategic maneuvers.
Talented Illustrator Makimura Shunsuke-san is the appointed character designer!</description></item><item><title>Metroid Prime Remastered</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3sda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3sda/</guid><description>Suit up for an iconic adventure
Intergalactic bounty hunter Samus Aran receives a distress signal from a wrecked frigate in orbit around planet Tallon IV. Upon investigation, the frigate reveals itself to be a Space Pirate research vessel home to terrifying genetic experiments using the mysterious Phazon substance. There, Samus encounters her nemesis, Meta Ridley, whom she pursues to the surface of Tallon IV. It’s up to her alone to explore the planet’s interconnected regions, investigate its dark secrets, and end the intergalactic threat posed by Phazon.</description></item><item><title>Miraculous: Rise of the Sphinx</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5mha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5mha/</guid><description>Paris needs a hero! Once again, the city of lights is in trouble as it faces a new menace—the most threatening sentimonster ever created is about to take control! As you take on the personna’s of the globally renowned superheroez Ladybug and Cat Noir, you’ll need to unveil the diabolical plan hatched by archvillain Hawk Moth—and squash it! Immerse yourself into the magical world of Miraculous and level up your superpowers as you embark on your biggest journey yet!</description></item><item><title>Monark</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3hce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3hce/</guid><description>Includes the MONARK full game and the Casual Outfit Set, which contains the following 5 costumes:
Protagonist&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit Nozomi&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit Shinya&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit Ryotaro&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit Kokoro&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit</description></item><item><title>NHRA Championship Drag Racing: Speed for All</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6a8a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6a8a/</guid><description>Speed For All is the most authentic NHRA game ever, fully immersing players in the genuine teams, tracks, vehicles, tuning, and strategies of this fiercely competitive motorsport. Strap into the driver’s seat across a range of exciting game modes in your quest to become the ultimate drag racing champion.
5 NHRA Classes: Top Fuel, Funny Car, Pro Stock, Pro Mod, &amp;amp; Super Modi¬ed 38 Top NHRA Drivers: Brittany Force, Antron Brown, John Force, Steve Torrence and more!</description></item><item><title>Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2gla/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2gla/</guid><description>Brawl it out as your favorite Nickelodeon characters in bombastic platform battles! With a power-packed cast of heroes from the Nickelodeon universe, face-off with all-stars from SpongeBob SquarePants, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, The Loud House, Danny Phantom, Aaahh!!! Real Monsters, The Wild Thornberrys, Hey Arnold!, Rugrats, and more to determine ultimate animation dominance. With unique move sets and attacks inspired by their personalities, each character has an individual style of play enabling endless action for Nickelodeon’s legion of fans.</description></item><item><title>NieR: Automata - The End of YoRHa Edition</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a532a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a532a/</guid><description>NieR:Automata The End of YoRHa Edition is the Nintendo Switch™ version of NieR:Automata, an award-winning post-apocalyptic action RPG that has achieved deep-rooted popularity around the world.
The distant future…
Invaders from another world attack without warning, unleashing a new type of threat: weapons known as “machine lifeforms.” In the face of this insurmountable threat, mankind is driven from Earth and takes refuge on the Moon. As 2B, a member of the newly organized android military force YoRHa, players will immerse themselves in a ferocious battle to take back the planet.</description></item><item><title>Ori - The Collection</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a349a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a349a/</guid><description>Contains two games
Ori and the Blind Forest: Definitive Edition Ori and the Will of the Wisps</description></item><item><title>Pac Man World</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a46tc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a46tc/</guid><description>PAC-MAN arrives home on his birthday to find the Ghosts have kidnapped PAC-MAN’s family and ruined his party! Off to the rescue, PAC-MAN sets out to Ghost Island!
• With improved UI, fine-tuned mechanics and updated visuals, PAC-MAN WORLD Re-PAC is a modernized classic! • Dodge Ghosts, solve environmental puzzles, rescue the PAC-FAM, and more in this platforming adventure! • Butt-bounce, rev-roll, PAC-DOT attack, and hover-jump to the final face-off against TOC-MAN!</description></item><item><title>Pathway</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3t9a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3t9a/</guid><description>LIMITED RUN #124
In 1936, Nazi influence has spread, along with rumours of secret excavations, mysterious artefacts, and gruesome occult rituals… Assemble a bold team of adventurers and journey through the desert-wilderness. Outwit foes in strategic squad combat and locate ancient treasures before they fall into the wrong hands!
Discover 5 different campaigns of varying difficulty, each attempt generating a new web of events…
Encounter hand-crafted story events. Search the well?</description></item><item><title>PAW Patrol - Grand Prix</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6nba/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6nba/</guid><description>Race around Adventure Bay with all your favorite PAW Patrol pups and up to 4 players at once – but look out for the obstacles left by mischievous Mayor Humdinger!
WIN THE PUP CUP!
The PAW Patrol are on their fastest mission yet – To win the Pup Cup! Drive around iconic locations including Adventure Bay, Jake’s Snowboarding Resort and The Jungle to find out who will be crowned the winner.</description></item><item><title>Potion Permit</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2hea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2hea/</guid><description>The town of Moonbury has always been wary of the advances of the outside world, preferring to rely on their traditional methods of healing. Until one day, when the mayor&amp;rsquo;s daughter falls ill, and the local witch doctor can do nothing to help her, they are forced to look outside their small community for help. The Medical Association decides to send their most accomplished chemist - you - to help cure the mayor&amp;rsquo;s daughter and convince the residents of Moonbury of the wonders of modern alchemy.</description></item><item><title>Process of Elimination</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a28sb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a28sb/</guid><description>The Quartering Duke, an infamous serial killer with over a hundred victims, has thrown the country into chaos with his heinous acts. To bring an end to his killing spree, the “Detective Alliance,” composed of the world’s top detectives, has gathered to uncover and subdue him.
However, in a series of unforeseen events, an aspiring yet unremarkable detective named Wato Hojo stumbles into their operations. He joins the Detective Alliance on the mysterious island of Morgue to investigate the Quartering Duke, only to make the gruesome discovery that their target lurks among them!</description></item><item><title>Save me Mr Tako: Definitive Edition</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3uka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3uka/</guid><description>SWITCH LIMITED RUN #147
Dive into a great adventure in the classic handheld era!
In a world where humans and octopuses are at war, Tako is a pacifist little octopus who rescues a woman from drowning one stormy night. A fairy sees this act of bravery and grants him the ability to survive on land. As he travels across the world, Tako defies his family and his people to try to resolve conflicts between humans and octopuses, plunging him into the very roots of this dysfunctional world.</description></item><item><title>Slime Rancher: Plortable Edition</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3yna/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3yna/</guid><description>Slime Rancher is the tale of Beatrix LeBeau, a plucky, young rancher who sets out for a life a thousand light years away from Earth on the ‘Far, Far Range’ where she tries her hand at making a living wrangling slimes.
Includes the Secret Style Pack DLC!
-Grow crops and raise chickadoos to feed your collection of hungry slimes. -Complete daily requests from other ranchers to get bonus rewards. -Earn money to upgrade your vacpack, build more corrals, or expand your ranch.</description></item><item><title>Smashing the Battle - Ghost Soul</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a45sb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a45sb/</guid><description>Gameplay - Smashing the Battle is a hack-and-slash action game. You battle against robots using standard attacks, as well as combo attacks. By crushing the enemy, you can open up the way forward. By attacking the enemy, you can gain skill points, allowing you to unleash devastating attacks on large groups of enemies all at once. After clearing each stage, use the coins you have collected to strengthen your character, allowing you to take on even more enemies.</description></item><item><title>Sonic Frontiers</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a39za/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a39za/</guid><description>Worlds are colliding in Sonic the Hedgehog’s newest high-speed adventure! In search of the missing Chaos emeralds, Sonic becomes stranded on an ancient island teeming with unusual creatures. Battle hordes of powerful enemies as you explore a breathtaking world of action, adventure, and mystery. Accelerate to new heights and experience the thrill of high-velocity, open-zone platforming freedom as you race across the five massive Starfall Islands. Jump into adventure, wield the power of the Ancients, and fight to stop these new mysterious foes.</description></item><item><title>Sonic Origins Plus</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6asg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a6asg/</guid><description>16 Classic Titles, 1 Timeless Collection The Blue Blur is back with an expanded multi-game collection of classic Sonic the Hedgehog games - Sonic Origins Plus!
Sonic Origins Plus features the four beloved classic titles in Sonic Origins – Sonic the Hedgehog, Sonic 2, Sonic 3 &amp;amp; Knuckles, and Sonic CD with remastered visuals, bonus characters, added modes, challenges, behind-the-scenes content and more, while adding significant improvements.
This bundle also includes 12 Sonic Game Gear titles, previously released add-on content, playable Knuckles in Sonic CD, and for the first time ever, Amy Rose as a playable character in Sonic the Hedgehog 1, 2, Sonic 3 &amp;amp; Knuckles, and Sonic CD!</description></item><item><title>SpongeBob: Krusty Cook-Off</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a24ab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a24ab/</guid><description>Let’s get cookin’! - Join SpongeBob SquarePants on a hilarious culinary adventure through the restaurants and kitchens of Bikini Bottom! When Mr. Krabs realizes there’s more money to be earned in the fast-food business, the penny-pinching entrepreneur sets out to expand his restaurant empire starting with a breakfast stand outside of SpongeBob’s house…and who better to help him run it than SpongeBob SquarePants himself? Create your own Bikini Bottom kitchen, decorate and customize your restaurant, and get ready to serve up delicious food to your guests!</description></item><item><title>Star Wars Racer &amp;amp; Commando Combo</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4uja/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4uja/</guid><description>Get two classic Star Wars™ games with theStar Wars™ Racer and Commando Combo which includes Star Wars™: Episode I Racer and the Star Wars™ Republic Commando.
Climb on, strap in, and experience the pure adrenaline-pumping excitement of the Podracing sequence from Star Wars™: Episode I The Phantom Menace in Star Wars™: Episode I Racer.
In the Star Wars™ Republic Commandoyou are the leader of your elite squad of Republic Commandos. Your mission is to infiltrate, dominate, and ultimately, annihilate the enemy.</description></item><item><title>Tactics Ogre: Reborn</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2v2a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2v2a/</guid><description>Based on the 2010 release, the game features improved graphics and sound, as well as updated game design, bringing to life a new Tactics Ogre that remains true to its roots. Tactics Ogre veterans will experience a game that surpasses their fondest memories, while players new to Tactics Ogre will discover a game unlike any they&amp;rsquo;ve ever played. Reborn and deeper than ever, the game enables players to immerse themselves in the world and intrigue of Tactics Ogre like never before.</description></item><item><title>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Cowabunga Collection</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a42sa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a42sa/</guid><description>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Cowabunga Collection assembles thirteen classic TMNT games by Konami in one incredible package. This collection provides a unique opportunity for gamers to experience these immensely popular and very influential games on Nintendo Switch™ and includes a fantastic set of new quality of life features:
Added Online Play* for certain games and Local Couch Play Save Anytime and Rewind Eleven Japanese Regional Version Releases Button Mapping Unique Development Art &amp;amp; Sketches Historic TMNT Media Content</description></item><item><title>Thank you</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/thank-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/thank-you/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The DioField Chronicle</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5tba/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5tba/</guid><description>A gritty and immersive story brought to life with the latest technology. Introducing &amp;quot;Real Time Tactical Battle&amp;quot; (RTTB), a new, deeply strategic, real-time battle system. The beginnings of a new Strategy RPG, crafted by a skilled and experienced development team.
■An all-new Strategy RPG that chronicles an epic tale of war and honour. Featuring a unique and beautiful world that blends fantasy, medieval and modern-day influences, and a deep yet innovative real-time battle system.</description></item><item><title>The House of the Dead: Remake</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a32da/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a32da/</guid><description>The famous Zombie shooter is back in a full remake. Renew with the spirit of Arcade from the nineties with the remake of this iconic shooter! Scientist and expert on the Human Genome Theory, Dr. Roy Curien, descends into madness as he searches for a power allowing him to resurrect the dead. After he succeeds, one of the researchers named Sophie Richards manages to contact her AMS friends Thomas Rogan and Agent G for help.</description></item><item><title>The Legend of Heroes - Trails from Zero</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a478a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a478a/</guid><description>Lloyd Bannings returns to his hometown to follow his late brother&amp;rsquo;s footsteps and join the Crossbell Police Department. However, he finds himself assigned to a ragtag new division called the Special Support Section, which performs odd jobs and helps people in need. But he and his new teammates slowly discover that their vibrant city hides a dark criminal underbelly&amp;hellip;as well as a few terrible secrets.</description></item><item><title>The Legend of Heroes: Trails into Reverie</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a475a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a475a/</guid><description>What destinies await these three fateful figures? Use the Crossroads system to switch between Rean Schwarzer, Lloyd Bannings, and the masked figure &amp;quot;C&amp;quot;, and determine the fates of key characters and locations within Zemuria. Dive into refined tactical combat with new features such as United Front, and discover new allies and challenges within the halls of the True Reverie Corridor!
Where one trail ends, another begins&amp;hellip; ​ The intertwining fates of three figures in Zemuria will be decided in this climactic chapter of The Legend of Heroes series!</description></item><item><title>Tin Hearts</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2lsa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2lsa/</guid><description>Behind every brilliant invention, hides an incredible story. From the makers of the critically acclaimed Fable series comes Tin Hearts – an immersive puzzle game wrapped in a powerful tale of love and compromise.
Discover an epic tale spanning generations and dimensions. G guide a troop of mischievous tin soldiers through a world full of beauty, magic, and mystery, using a variety of whimsical and inventive contraptions to bounce, shoot and glide them to their goal.</description></item><item><title>Train Life: A Railway Simulator</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4p5a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4p5a/</guid><description>For the first time in a railway simulator, you are the driver and the company manager!
TAKE THE CONTROL OF YOUR TRAIN AND TRAVEL TO EUROPE Drive your passengers or goods across 10 countries and explore the countryside, towns, forests, and mountains of Europe from your cab. Each locomotive has its own characteristics (power, braking, etc.), and you need to learn to control it expertly while following the railway signs and adapting to the weather conditions.</description></item><item><title>Yurukill: The Calumniation Games</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5bwb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a5bwb/</guid><description>Accused of a horrific crime you didn’t commit, you find yourself in Yurukill Land—a mysterious amusement park filled with life threatening attractions you must survive if you desire freedom. Writer Homura Kawamoto, best known for his hit title Kakegurui, writes a twisted and multifaceted story that will keep you wanting more. In addition to an in-depth story, Yurukill also features shoot-‘em-up gameplay by renowned developer G.Rev, and online leaderboards allowing players to see how they rank among the competition.</description></item></channel></rss>