<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homepage on Jammy</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in Homepage on Jammy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://demo-shop.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Annulled</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/cancel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/cancel/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Are You Smarter than a 5th Grader?</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4cpa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4cpa/</guid><description>Are You Smarter Than A 5th Grader? for Nintendo® Switch is a charmingly humorous quiz game based on the popular TV franchise. Multiple-choice questions, true-or-false challenges, and minigames will test your proficiency in 24 different subjects. Faced with a tough question, you can always rely on your classmates for help. More than 6800 questions on topics like animal sciences, vocabulary, math, and more are delivered by a diverse, fully voiced, and animated cast of characters.</description></item><item><title>Astalon: Tears of the Earth</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2r8a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2r8a/</guid><description>LIMITED RUN #138 Relive the glory days of 8-bit action-adventure through beautifully detailed, authentic pixel art set in a dark, fantastic world! Astalon features the progressive exploration of an interconnected world with the swiftness and quick rhythm of a room-by-room action platformer.
Original character design by Ryusuke Mita, creator of world-famous manga Dragon Half! Play at your own pace &amp;ndash; explore thoroughly and build your characters strengths, or use risky methods to slice your way up the tower furiously!</description></item><item><title>Aztech Forgotten Gods</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3pga/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3pga/</guid><description>Aztech Forgotten Gods is the cyber-stone action-adventure following Achtli, a young woman who battles the colossal Forgotten Gods. To uncover the truth behind her far-future Mesoamerican metropolis, she&amp;rsquo;ll have to turn the Gods&amp;rsquo; power against them, as she soars through the city with power and grace.</description></item><item><title>Blaster Master Zero 3</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3jxa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3jxa/</guid><description>LIMITED RUN #109
Blaster Master Zero 3&amp;rsquo;s hybrid of sidescrolling and top-down action is back for its 3rd chapter, and more intense than ever before! Series protagonist Jason travels to where the series all began, the planet Sophia, in order to save series heroine Eve in this final installment of the BMZ trilogy.
In the previous game, Blaster Master Zero 2, Jason and his partner Eve finally reach their destination, the planet Sophia, after a long and arduous journey through space.</description></item><item><title>Cart</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/cart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/cart/</guid><description/></item><item><title>checkout</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/before-stripe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/before-stripe/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Curse of the Sea Rats</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2mxa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2mxa/</guid><description>Curse of the Sea Rats is a ‘ratoidvania’ platform adventure with lovingly crafted, hand-drawn animations. Embark on the epic journey of four prisoners of the British empire, transformed into rats by the notorious pirate witch, Flora Burn. To regain their human bodies, they will have to fight dangerous bosses, uncover the secrets of the vast Irish coast, and ultimately capture the witch who cursed them.</description></item><item><title>Doom: The Classics Collection</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4kya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4kya/</guid><description>Limited Run # 102 Includes three classic DOOM games preserved on one cartridge - DOOM, DOOM II, and DOOM 3! No game downloads required. These classic games popularized the first-person shooter and allow players to wield an arsenal of powerful weapons as you battle demon hordes on Mars, on Earth, and across Hell. DOOM: You’re one of Earth’s toughest marines stationed on mars when a military experiment opens the gates to hell.</description></item><item><title>Dragon Star Varnir</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2r3b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2r3b/</guid><description>In a world where the bones of an ancient beast tower over the land&amp;hellip;​​
The Knight Zephy is part of an order whose role is to hunt down witches – people seen as cursed beings for giving birth to dragons.​​
He is brutally mauled by a dragon on one mission, but as he gasps his last breath, two witches save him by feeding him dragon blood – a death-defying magical substance that also grants him new witch powers.</description></item><item><title>DreamWorks Dragons: Legends of The Nine Realms</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4nxa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4nxa/</guid><description>Unleash your inner dragon and fly beyond the Hidden World, on your fiery adventure to rescue Thunder’s family and save the dragon kingdoms!
Feel the wind against your scales as you soar and dive through unexplored realms. Use your speed, tail, and claws to defeat the worthy foes and gigantic dragon bosses that stand in your way. Level up Thunder and his friends to become the ultimate dragon heroes by choosing new unlockable skills and powers.</description></item><item><title>Error 404</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/404.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/404.html</guid><description/></item><item><title>Golden Force</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2qka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2qka/</guid><description>The King of Demons sets his sights on Muscle Island, a peaceful paradise where life is good and all is well. Yet this evil monster sends in his army and attacks the populace with the help of his Wasting their last coins in the island’s taverns, mercenaries from the powerful Golden Force enjoy their last moments of vacation when they receive a new contract: defeat this evil threat in order to win back the Gold Mountain now in the Demon King’s possession.</description></item><item><title>Hello Neighbor 2</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4t3a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4t3a/</guid><description>Hello Neighbor 2 is the sequel to the popular stealth horror game about sneaking into your creepy neighbor&amp;rsquo;s house. You play as a local journalist investigating missing person reports when you follow a series of clues leading you back to the abandoned house of The Neighbor.
The only problem is, that it&amp;rsquo;s occupied by a mysterious crow-like being. The only logical thing to do is break in. Welcome back to Raven Brooks.</description></item><item><title>Horgihugh And Friends</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4u6b/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4u6b/</guid><description>Shoot down 16-bit bad guys in Horgihugh and Friends!
At the end of a brutal war, countries decided to dismantle their weapons. When the Gozareans attack, two retired pilots realize their trusty vintage fighter planes are the only means of combating the alien’s powerful weapon-nullifying technologies. Taking to the skies, Hugh and Figaro are the world’s last wings of hope.</description></item><item><title>Kirby's Return to Dream Land Deluxe</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2jya/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2jya/</guid><description>The tough puff Kirby is back for a 4-player* platforming adventure. Copy enemies’ abilities and use their power to attack with a sword, wield a whip, and float with a parasol. You can also laser blast with the new Mecha Copy Ability that makes a series debut! The extra muscle will be handy in finding missing pieces for Magolor’s ship, which crash landed on Planet Popstar. Float and fight along with friends on the same system, where each player can control another Kirby or one of Kirby’s iconic friends like King Dedede, Meta Knight, and Bandana Waddle Dee.</description></item><item><title>Loop Hero</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4taa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4taa/</guid><description>Infinite Adventure: Select from unlockable character classes and deck cards before setting out on each expedition along a randomly generated loop path. No expedition is ever the same as the ones before it Plan Your Struggle: Strategically place building, terrain, and enemy cards along each loop to create your own dangerous path. Find balance between the cards to increase your chances of survival while recovering valuable loot and resources for your camp Loot and Upgrade: Strike down menacing creatures, recover stronger loot to equip on the fly and unlock new perks along the way Expand Your Camp: Turn hard-earned resources into campsite upgrades and gain valuable reinforcements with each completed loop along the expedition path Save the Lost World: Overcome a series of unholy guardian bosses over a grand saga to save the world and break the time loop of the Lich</description></item><item><title>Love Esquire</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2yrb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2yrb/</guid><description>In Love Esquire, you&amp;rsquo;re not a famous knight, but a good-for-nothing squire who&amp;rsquo;s on a quest to find man&amp;rsquo;s greatest pleasure. Getting the girl won&amp;rsquo;t be easy though, since most of them are waaaay out of your league!
So raise those stats, battle monsters, and unleash your full potential!
FEATURES
♡ 5 Dateable Waifus – Love Esquire&amp;rsquo;s heroines are not just pretty faces! Each have their own unique ambitions, backstories, plots, and dirty little secrets for you to uncover.</description></item><item><title>Mail Mole - Collector's Edition</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3aye/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3aye/</guid><description>We are presenting our new hero, Molty, the mail mole! Moving underground, climbing massive walls and soaring through the skies, there’s no place our hero can’t reach! Traveling with Cannon Lines, Molty must overcome the most complicated challenges to reach Carrotland‘s furthest mailboxes: bottomless pits, quicksands, avalanches, floating platforms, sharp spikes&amp;hellip; a tough road. But when the power is out, you can’t send an email! Embark on an adventure that will force you to make the most important delivery of your life.</description></item><item><title>Mario + Rabbids: Sparks of Hope</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2g7a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2g7a/</guid><description>Team up with Mario, Luigi, Princess Peach, Rabbid Peach, Rabbid Luigi, and their friends on a galactic journey to defeat a malevolent entity and save your Spark companions. Explore planets throughout the galaxy as you uncover mysterious secrets and compelling quests!
•Build your dream team with three heroes from an eclectic roster of nine. •Take down all new bosses, along with some familiar enemies throughout the galaxy. •Rescue the adorable Sparks throughout the galaxy, who provide distinct powers that will help you in battle.</description></item><item><title>Metroid Prime Remastered</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3sda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3sda/</guid><description>Suit up for an iconic adventure
Intergalactic bounty hunter Samus Aran receives a distress signal from a wrecked frigate in orbit around planet Tallon IV. Upon investigation, the frigate reveals itself to be a Space Pirate research vessel home to terrifying genetic experiments using the mysterious Phazon substance. There, Samus encounters her nemesis, Meta Ridley, whom she pursues to the surface of Tallon IV. It’s up to her alone to explore the planet’s interconnected regions, investigate its dark secrets, and end the intergalactic threat posed by Phazon.</description></item><item><title>Monark</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3hce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3hce/</guid><description>Includes the MONARK full game and the Casual Outfit Set, which contains the following 5 costumes:
Protagonist&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit Nozomi&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit Shinya&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit Ryotaro&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit Kokoro&amp;rsquo;s Casual Outfit</description></item><item><title>Nickelodeon All-Star Brawl</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2gla/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2gla/</guid><description>Brawl it out as your favorite Nickelodeon characters in bombastic platform battles! With a power-packed cast of heroes from the Nickelodeon universe, face-off with all-stars from SpongeBob SquarePants, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, The Loud House, Danny Phantom, Aaahh!!! Real Monsters, The Wild Thornberrys, Hey Arnold!, Rugrats, and more to determine ultimate animation dominance. With unique move sets and attacks inspired by their personalities, each character has an individual style of play enabling endless action for Nickelodeon’s legion of fans.</description></item><item><title>Pathway</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3t9a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3t9a/</guid><description>LIMITED RUN #124
In 1936, Nazi influence has spread, along with rumours of secret excavations, mysterious artefacts, and gruesome occult rituals… Assemble a bold team of adventurers and journey through the desert-wilderness. Outwit foes in strategic squad combat and locate ancient treasures before they fall into the wrong hands!
Discover 5 different campaigns of varying difficulty, each attempt generating a new web of events…
Encounter hand-crafted story events. Search the well?</description></item><item><title>Potion Permit</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2hea/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2hea/</guid><description>The town of Moonbury has always been wary of the advances of the outside world, preferring to rely on their traditional methods of healing. Until one day, when the mayor&amp;rsquo;s daughter falls ill, and the local witch doctor can do nothing to help her, they are forced to look outside their small community for help. The Medical Association decides to send their most accomplished chemist - you - to help cure the mayor&amp;rsquo;s daughter and convince the residents of Moonbury of the wonders of modern alchemy.</description></item><item><title>Save me Mr Tako: Definitive Edition</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3uka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3uka/</guid><description>SWITCH LIMITED RUN #147
Dive into a great adventure in the classic handheld era!
In a world where humans and octopuses are at war, Tako is a pacifist little octopus who rescues a woman from drowning one stormy night. A fairy sees this act of bravery and grants him the ability to survive on land. As he travels across the world, Tako defies his family and his people to try to resolve conflicts between humans and octopuses, plunging him into the very roots of this dysfunctional world.</description></item><item><title>Slime Rancher: Plortable Edition</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3yna/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a3yna/</guid><description>Slime Rancher is the tale of Beatrix LeBeau, a plucky, young rancher who sets out for a life a thousand light years away from Earth on the ‘Far, Far Range’ where she tries her hand at making a living wrangling slimes.
Includes the Secret Style Pack DLC!
-Grow crops and raise chickadoos to feed your collection of hungry slimes. -Complete daily requests from other ranchers to get bonus rewards. -Earn money to upgrade your vacpack, build more corrals, or expand your ranch.</description></item><item><title>Tactics Ogre: Reborn</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2v2a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2v2a/</guid><description>Based on the 2010 release, the game features improved graphics and sound, as well as updated game design, bringing to life a new Tactics Ogre that remains true to its roots. Tactics Ogre veterans will experience a game that surpasses their fondest memories, while players new to Tactics Ogre will discover a game unlike any they&amp;rsquo;ve ever played. Reborn and deeper than ever, the game enables players to immerse themselves in the world and intrigue of Tactics Ogre like never before.</description></item><item><title>Thank you</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/thank-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/checkout/thank-you/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Tin Hearts</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2lsa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a2lsa/</guid><description>Behind every brilliant invention, hides an incredible story. From the makers of the critically acclaimed Fable series comes Tin Hearts – an immersive puzzle game wrapped in a powerful tale of love and compromise.
Discover an epic tale spanning generations and dimensions. G guide a troop of mischievous tin soldiers through a world full of beauty, magic, and mystery, using a variety of whimsical and inventive contraptions to bounce, shoot and glide them to their goal.</description></item><item><title>Train Life: A Railway Simulator</title><link>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4p5a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://demo-shop.xyz/products/a4p5a/</guid><description>For the first time in a railway simulator, you are the driver and the company manager!
TAKE THE CONTROL OF YOUR TRAIN AND TRAVEL TO EUROPE Drive your passengers or goods across 10 countries and explore the countryside, towns, forests, and mountains of Europe from your cab. Each locomotive has its own characteristics (power, braking, etc.), and you need to learn to control it expertly while following the railway signs and adapting to the weather conditions.</description></item></channel></rss>